Let's now talk about user input.
现在让我们来谈一下用户输入
Gone are the days when websites purely delivered information to the user through
像以前那样通过浏览器给用户呈现
the browser.
纯信息的时代已经过去了
And at most they would have hyperlinks that you could click to
如果说那时有什么新奇的东西的话
move to other pages in the website.
也顶多是一些超链接
Most websites these days provide many different ways for
对于当今时代 大多数网站都提供了很多
the user to interact with the website.
和用户互动的元素
Say in the form of buttons or fonts that the user can fill out
比如说一些按钮或者一个用户能填写
information and submit to the server and so on.
一些提供给服务器的信息的表格
So let's look at some of these in more detail.
所以接下来让我们学习一些这方面的知识
To help us understand the various ways a website can provide for
为了让你更好地理解一个网站能提供怎样的 和用户互动的方式
users to interact, let's just quickly pay a visit to your course website.
让我们来看一下我们的课程页面
Now here you see a lot of buttons on the screen so
在这里你可以看到许多按钮
you can see a button that you can click.
你可以点击这些按钮
You can see a search box where you can type in information and
你还可以看到这里有个搜索框
then press this button in order to initiate a search.
你可以通过这个地方来搜索你想搜索的东西
You might have other buttons that you can click to
你可能还能看到一些
be able to cause some actions to be taken.
用于其它用途的按钮
You could even have hyperlinks on the website.
同时你也可以看到一些超链接
So hyperlinks still do exist on websites that will take you to other parts
这些超链接能将你导航到
of your website.
这个网站的其它地方
All the user inputs to your website boils down to three different
一般而言这些交互是通过
tags that can be used for this purpose.
三种标签来实现的
We have the  tag, which was originally designed for hyperlinks.
一种是标签它原本是用来 设计超链接的
So you have the h ref attribute for the a tag through which you can specify what
你可以通过 href 属性来指定这个超链接
should be done when the user clicks on the hyperlink.
导向的地方
Then we have buttons.
然后就是按钮
Buttons typically, the moment you put a button,
一般而言 当你用了按钮的时候
you are automatically prompting the user to click the button.
你就是在暗示用户去点击它
So that's how users would interact with buttons.
这是比较常见的一种交互方式
Button was added to the HTML specification later on to provide
不过在接下来的发展中 按钮在 HTML 规范里通常提供的是
a separate way from hyperlinks to enable user interaction.
不同于超链接的交互方式
Then of course we have forms.
然后就是表格了
Forms provide for more detailed interaction from the user.
表格提供了一种更详细的和用户交互的方式
User can submit information by typing in things into
用户可以通过在表格的各个输入框中键入信息
the various boxes that you provide, and then click a button in
然后点击某些按钮来上传这些信息
order to submit the information that you entered into the form.
然后你就可以利用这些信息来做进一步的工作
Buttons themselves are a very
按钮本身就是一个非常直白的
straightforward way of providing interaction to the user.
与用户交互的东西
Once you put a button, you're expecting the user to click on that button.
所以当你使用按钮时你要注意 这意味着你期待着用户点击它
Button behavior can
按钮的行为也是多种多样的
vary depending on where the button is positioned within your website.
这主要要看你在你网页中的何处 放置了这个按钮
If a button is included inside a form, the general expectation is that when you click
如果按钮被放在一个表格中 那么通常情况下它都承担着
on the button the form information will be submitted.
上传表格内容的工作
Buttons outside the form may take on many other roles.
在表格外的按钮则可以用很多功能
So clicking on a button may open or hide parts of information in your webpage.
比如说切换某些信息的显隐状态
Maybe open a model on the screen that
又或是打开一个能够让你
allows you to view other information.
浏览其它信息的一个模态框
So we will see some of these uses of buttons in the next module.
我们将会在下一个单元中学习 这些功能的具体细节
The  tag itself has many times been hijacked
标签经常被用成其它用途
and transformed into a button through the use of CSS.
这可以通过 CSS 类来实现
Indeed even Bootstrap itself you can easily turn an a tag into
事实上 Bootstrap 本身就能轻易地将一个 a 标签
a button-like form very easily.
转化成一个长得像按钮的东西
Which is something that we will see in the later lectures and exercise.
我们将在后面某几节课和练习中 学习其具体实现
Forms, of course, are the grandaddy of information submission.
而表格 几乎天生就是上传信息的料
They provide you with many different fields that you can fill in,
它们可以提供许多你能输入的框
input fields that allow you to specify different kinds of inputs.
它甚至允许你定制特定输入框的规格要求
And then we have text areas which are much larger
如果你需要一些详细信息
boxes which allow you to fill in more detailed information.
你也可以加入一个文字区域
You could have buttons of course, within a form that allows
要注意的是 一般要加入一个按钮
the triggering of the submission of the information that you enter into the form.
来让用户将他们输入的东西上传
Then you have select.
表格中还可以有下拉菜单
And select allows you to select from a predetermined set of choices,
它会让用户从预先设定好的 一些选项中选出一个
then you have checkboxes, then you have radio buttons.
然后就是复选框和单选按钮 等等等等
So all of these combinations allow
所有这些加在一起 让表格能够获取
forms to be very versatile in seeking information from the user.
用户的多种多样的信息
So in the next set of lectures we're gonna review Bootstrap Button Classes and
所以在接下来的几节课中 我们将学习 Bootstrap 的按钮类
then subsequently we'll look at Bootstrap Classes to style forms.
和定制表格的一些 Bootstrap 的类 【翻译 - Carefree0910】